The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight,
and despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
The Captains held a meeting to decide who would go to train in the Heart Kingdom.
Five of the Black Bulls.
Asta.
Nero.
Luck.
Finral.
And Noelle.
Mimosa from the Golden Dawn.
Leopold of the Crimson Lion Kings.
Captain Charlotte chose to nominate herself,
as did Captain Rill from the Aqua Deer.
This elite group would be learning from the Five Spirit Guardians.
Afterward, during the decoration ceremony,
those who had performed especially well in the last conflict were recognized.
Leopold, Soul, and Mimosa received promotions.
Then...
You're being promoted as well, Yuno.
To First Class Senior Magic Knight.
Huh?
Yuno was promoted to the highest rank below Captain.
The King, not to be outdone, made his own promotion.
By my authority as ruler of this kingdom,
I award to Seke the title of First Class Senior Magic Knight!
Did he say First Class Senior Magic Knight?
That's like the cream of the crop!
Surprisingly, Seke was given the same prestigious title as Yuno.
Back at the Black Bull's hideout,
there was one squad member who refused to accept his exclusion from training in the Heart Kingdom.
Please, boss. I'm begging you here.
If I'm going to be a real man, then I refuse to be left behind anymore.
I'll go even if you tell me to stay here.
You good with that?
Yes, sir!
I can push past the limits of my mana!
More than any commoner has before!
Alright.
I'll ask Julius if there's room for another guy.
And at the Golden Dawn's headquarters,
not everyone was pleased to hear about the promotion that the Wizard King had awarded to Yuno.
A First Class Senior Magic Knight, huh?
Now he's the same rank as Vice, Kath, and Longris.
Which is crazy since he's only been with us for a year.
I'm not exactly surprised. Yuno's really powerful.
Come to think of it, Longris hasn't been on a mission since everything that happened with the Midnight Sun.
If you ask me, it's only a matter of time before Yuno takes his job.
Ever since he got that promotion, it's all anyone talks about around here.
For good reason.
Yuno and Longris are both amazing mages and all,
but when it comes to who would be a better VC,
I gotta tell you, the answer is pretty obvious.
Oh! Vice Captain Longris, sir!
Hello there!
Out for a stroll?
It's a wonderful day for it!
Please enjoy!
I should go!
It's only a matter of time before Yuno takes his job.
So,
何度も 何度も 何度も 目の前の今を超えるさ
何度も 何度も 何度も 涙を希望に変えていこう
七色の 日常を進め 永遠に光れ
Shine like a demon
天使と 悪魔が 交際してく
世界は 矛盾だらけさ
思い通りじゃない
そのくらいで 負ける夢はダサい
So, 何度も 何度も 何度も 夢の前の壁を超えるさ
何度も 何度も 良さを未来に繋げよう
何度も 何度も 未来に繋げよう
何度も 未来に繋げよう
何度も 光れ
You shine like a diamond
Don't you think it's about time?
Time for what, sir?
To continue with your duties as vice-captain
We'll be dealing with Spade soon
So I need you to watch over the squad
I can't yet
Please just wait a little longer
Has my brother contacted you recently?
Oh yes, look
He writes to you?
It's funny
He could use portals to visit me anytime
But he's been sending letters through them instead
I'm sure he's trying to put a little distance between you two
Because he believes it's part of his training
Do you feel cold?
You're looking especially lovely today, Noelle
Let's go for some tea
Huh?
You have to stop or you're never going to break your cursed funeral
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
What's he saying in his letters?
That he's going to train in the Heart Kingdom soon
He told you that?
If he has to travel to another land
It must be for something serious
Do you think there's going to be another big battle?
I tried to get him to tell me face to face
You know, since he's not very good at keeping secrets
What's wrong, Longris?
There's no need to concern yourself with that, Lady Finnis
Why the smile?
You can't hide things either
The two of you really are a lot alike
Don't ever compare me to him!
Please forgive me
No, it's fine
I'm sorry
Are you alright?
Yes
You should go back inside and rest
I'll take my leave now
It's just my usual cough
Nothing too scary
Either way, I've got business to attend to today
Oh, did you return to your post as the Vice Captain?
Goodbye
Thank you for the tea
That's check
What a clever move
See that?
You lose, Alecdora
Told you it was better to bet on Shirin
Isn't it obvious?
The game's not even over yet
Come on, Yuno! This is amazing weather for a date!
Where should we go?
I'm good with anything, honestly
Hey! Are you listening?
Here comes Vice Captain Longris
What's your problem?
I know you're jealous that Yuno and I are the perfect couple
But that's no reason to have such an attitude
What's wrong? You need something?
I'd like to spar with you
You're a first-class Senior Magic Knight now
So based on that, you and I should be equally matched
I want to test you and determine whether you're qualified to do it
Let's do it
You know
Calm down, both of you!
Let's not be rash!
There's no reason for this
No, Klaus
You're the one who needs to calm down
I'm not suggesting this because I want to pick a fight with him
Come
Pardon me, sir
I had to tell you that the Vice Captain just challenged Yuno to a duel
Did he really?
It makes me nervous
I hope nothing terrible happens
Hmm
I'll be with you the whole time, Yuno
So trust me, you don't need to worry about holding back
A normal sparring session is no fun
Let's spice it up
How about this
How about this?
The loser agrees to resign from the Golden Dawn
Oop
Honestly, what a vulgar bunch they are
You should really choose your friends more carefully, Yuno
Aren't you embarrassed to be seen with people like that?
What a vulgar bunch they are
Honestly, what a vulgar bunch they are
You should really choose your friends more carefully, Yuno
Aren't you embarrassed to be seen with people like that?
Why would I be?
I've never felt that way once
I'm very proud of Osta
He's my rival
A simpleton like that's your rival?
And for what, anyway?
Are you a rival?
A simpleton like that's your rival?
And for what, anyway?
What a vulgar bunch they are
Honestly, what a vulgar bunch they are
You should really choose your friends more carefully, Yuno
Aren't you embarrassed to be seen with people like that?
Why would I be?
I've never felt that way once
I'm very proud of Osta
He's my rival
A simpleton like that's your rival?
And for what, anyway?
Are you two in some kind of competition?
That's right, yes
We're aiming to become the Wizard King
I don't know what your problem is, sir, Smirky
But I don't let anybody mock my Yuno
There's no rule saying that a commoner can't be the Wizard King
Huh?
First, of course, I'll become captain of the Golden Dawn
Will you?
Have you forgotten the fact that I'm our squad's current vice-captain?
I believe you said, before you're Wizard King
You want to be captain of our squad, yes?
If you win, you'll be forcing the vice-captain to abandon the team
Which would put you one step closer to the top
That's not such a bad deal, is it?
Stop talking and let's go
He keeps adding more and more fuel to the fire
I don't think they can resolve this quickly, no
I have a feeling this may get quite bloody
Let's make some bets
Why are you like this, Steven?
We should stop them
Now are you ready, Yuno?
Let's begin!
He made the rock disappear
Talking won't solve this
Please stop it, vice-captain!
He's out to kill!
Why?
Oh dear
Looks like you dodged it
But I'll get you this time!
Wind creation magic
Wind plate shower!
Perhaps I was too careless
My goodness, that's quite a scowl
I don't know why you've been holding back on me so far
But I'd like you to stop it now
Oh, you think I've been holding back, do you?
Of course
If you hadn't been, you would have dodged that last spell easily
Longris, fight me for real or you'll get hurt
This isn't right
Actually, I have a feeling Yuno isn't doing that to provoke him
What did you say to me?
You want me to say it slower for you?
I was giving you the benefit of the doubt
But now I know you're trying to insult me
I won't go easy on you anymore!
It's that spell again
This is the same spatial magic you used during the Royal Knights selection exam
I'll go all out! Happy now?
Spirit Assimilation
Spirit Dive
Take this!
Monozone
Spirit Hush Dance
Incredible!
Yuno's really talented
Spirit Storm
I know this move
It's from when that elf was possessing him
The auto-defense spell
He shouldn't be able to use it anymore
Now that he's been released from the spirit's influence
It's faint
But I can still feel the mana from the elf that was reincarnated inside my body
Well, you can't keep dodging me forever!
He just hit Yuno's crown
It's been destroyed
Can't you do anything besides run away?!
It's all over!
Yuno!
Well, how?
An after image?
You're right
It is over
Oh good!
I've survived!
But this means the vice-captain's leaving
You don't happen to remember who I bet on
Don't know, don't care!
So that's how it is
Don't just stand there
Go ahead, laugh at me
I gave it all I had and you still won
You did get serious
But not till it was half done
Before that you were trying to lose
Quite an accusation
But you're right
I wanted to let you take me down
It was a plan for me to resign with some dignity
But this... this is shameful
I lost
Even without holding back
That isn't shameful at all
Do you think it was that easy for me to win against you?
He brings up a good point
That's right, it was a close battle
What makes you think that matters?!
You just defeated me!
And that's all I care about!
Which means that I'm going to walk away from the Golden Dawn
That's what we agreed upon
I never actually agreed to those terms
Maybe you didn't accept them, but I did
This is stupid
Take good care of the squad for me, you know
You're walking away now?
Do you honestly feel like you lost that battle?
If you'd have gone all out from the start
Then you might have succeeded
Someday down the road
Let's spar again
And promise you won't hold back
Come back
Forgive me for not consulting you, Captain
I'm not surprised
You know, Longris
You didn't have to resort to theatrics because you wanted to resign
You saw through me too?
Sorry, that's the way I am
I'm well aware
But then, I also know that this isn't the end of your journey
What happened today doesn't change the fact that you're part of the Golden Dawn
Thank you very much
I should go
I'll be waiting
We all will
Longris, why are you dressed like that?
I'm about to leave on a journey
What?
So it's true then, you really did leave the Golden Dawn
Well, no, not entirely
I just made a silly promise and now I have to keep my word
Oh
Good morning, Lady Finnis, how are you?
Uh, uh, Longris?
What are you wearing that big cloak for?
Let me guess, you wanted to pay one cent
One final visit to Lady Finnis before you went away for your training, right?
Huh?
Yeah, I did
I'll be the man who makes Lady Finnis happy
I promise, once again, I'll be the man who makes Lady Finnis happy
I promise, once I've become worthy, I'm gonna come back for you
I guess I'm willing to wait for you
I'll be the man who makes Lady Finnis happy
I promise, once I've become worthy, I'm gonna come back for you
I guess, what are you wearing that big cloak for?
Let me guess, you wanted to pay one final visit to Lady Finnis before you went away for your training, right?
Huh?
Yeah, I did
I'll be the man who makes Lady Finnis happy
I promise, once I've become worthy, I'm gonna come back for you
I guess I'm willing to wait, but don't take too long
By the way, there's something I forgot to tell you
Despite how you feel, I still haven't decided to let you win her love
Come now, just who do you think you are, brother?
Wait and see, our battle is only beginning
You'll need energy to train in the Heart Kingdom, so you gotta get way more food!
Gladly! This is great!
I'm gonna be so sick
Is it just you three?
Yeah, lucky Magnus said they were gonna wait and have their dinner later on, if that's cool, sir
Gotcha!
If you notice me, then I'm sure you'll invite me to go to the Heart Kingdom with you too
However, I plan to improve my curse magic under my father's guidance
So I have to go back home now
It pains me, but I cannot join you
I'll just leave without pain, see?
I'll just rest all my limits and part of my appetite!
Wow, did someone just walk past us?
Nah, it was the wind
Oh, okay
And Yami
Did they say they'd let me go or not?
Don't worry, Magna, they're alright with you tagging along
Wow, thanks a million, boss!
You should thank the Wizard King, not me
That's badass!
I'm so happy you're coming with us, Magna
I appreciate it, pal
I could go for a nice cold drink
Wait, what's that juice?
You know, the tasty one they have in Heart
Tasty?
Oh, were you talking about the crimson orange juice?
Right, I can't wait to try that!
I hear it gets sweeter when you add your mana to it
It gets sweeter?
Yeah, but if you're me, it just stays all sour and disgusting
Quit crying, at least you had me there to fix it for you
Anyway, you guys will arrive in the Heart Kingdom tomorrow
Make the Black Bulls proud
And push past your limits
Yes, sir!
I'm going to improve my magic ability
So that I can defeat the Devil Megicula
I can defeat the Devil Megicula
So that I can defeat it
That I can defeat the remedial Point
Hope I'm on my way
Haleに転んで傷ついて
気づけば誰ももうどこにもいない
me
oh
so
See you next time.
If you're going to quit being vice-captain,
forgive me for not consulting you, Captain.
Since you gave up your post, you're on lunch duty.
So you're still making me work?
You don't like it. Then clean the chalkboard.
The chalkboard! That's just as terrible!
I can always put you in charge of the animals.
Since when do we have these?
You suck!
Ten, two, three!
I'm going to work so hard I'll have muscles on my muscle!
Would you be quiet? Try training your brain for once instead.
Black Clover, page 155. The Five Spirit Guardians.